We're here today with
director Chang Hang-jun and J. Y. Park.
It's the 33rd year
since J. Y. Park's debut.
MADE HIS SOLO DEBUT IN 1994
Over those 30 years…
-Seriously.
-…he has produced many artists,
and recently,
he's been taking part in state affairs.
-Many people are quite curious.
-Right?
So can you tell us exactly what you do?
It's called the Presidential Committee
on Popular Culture Exchange.
We're currently planning
a K-culture festival
that'll launch
on December 2nd of next year.
-A festival?
-I see.
It's a festival and an awards show
titled Fanomenon.
We took the word "phenomenon"
and changed the first part to "fan."
It means a phenomenon created by fans.
We plan to award the fans
in different cultural fields,
such as K-pop, K-film, and K-drama.
That sounds fun.
TOTALLY!
If we systematize this,
it'll become something we can pass on.
While we waited briefly outside,
I listened to what he had to say.
The whole project is huge,
and I was there thinking,
"Why hadn't anyone thought of this?"
I thought he was perfect for the job.
If someone hears him in passing,
they'll think he sounds
like a typical con man.
Yes, you're right!
RATHER SUSPICIOUS
-If it weren't J. Y. Park, that is.
-Yes.
But when he said it…
It sounds credible.
Yes, I'm looking forward to it.
I personally want to ask you
to throw in soccer too.
I'm not in charge of sports.
WHAT A SHAME
Chef & My Fridge should join it.
There is a cooking part.
OH MY, CAN WE JOIN?
-We can join.
-It'll truly be a global festival.
In the midst of your busy schedule,
-he even released a new song.
-Really?
Tell us about it.
It's called "WET."
-"WET"?
-Like soaked?
Soaked. W-E-T, wet.
It's like, "Make me covered in sweat."
THE MEANING BEHIND THE LYRICS
I'm not saying
it has a dirty meaning.
-We weren't thinking that.
-No one said that.
-Your clothes get wet when you work out.
-Yes.
-That's it.
-"Let me dance and have fun."
AN UPBEAT DANCE TRACK FOR THE SUMMER
I heard you released "WET"
solely for a single performance.
Which one are you referring to?
I'm probably performing right now
as this show is airing.
-What?
-I see.
WATERBOMB Festival.
As a man in his fifties, I was surprised
when I got the offer last year.
So I asked my agency,
"Do I say yes? Wouldn't I seem too silly?"
But everyone told me to go.
So I did, and the response
was much more positive than I thought.
This year, the festival wanted
to use my song as the campaign song.
Really?
The thing is that
he holds the record
for the oldest performer of the festival.
THE OLDEST ON CHEF & MY FRIDGE
-And that's not an easy feat.
-It's not.
So we prepared a video
of his performance there
from last year.
-The pride of those in their 50s.
-Yes.
What was his performance like last year?
WATERBOMB FESTIVAL
WATERBOMB Festival, the peak of summer.
WALKS UP AS JYPINK
WHOA
LET'S GET THE PLASTIC PANTS GOING
WEARING A HALTERNECK TOP
How do you like my back?
I love it.
IT'S AWESOME
OWNED THE WATERBOMB FESTIVAL
I want to go and see it.
AN IMPRESSIVE PERFORMANCE
-You're in great shape.
-Totally
He must put in a lot of effort.
Was it your idea to wear that outfit?
I thought everyone would expect me
to show up in plastic pants,
so I asked people on my social media,
"What should I wear?"
People began to comment things like,
"You already know"
-and "That one."
-"That one."
About 97% of the comments
said plastic pants.
But a plastic outfit is tough to dance in,
so I decided to wear a halterneck top.
That was why.
He had a reason.
This year,
you can look forward to it.
SO CURIOUS
I'm using a new material.
WILL USE A NEW MATERIAL THIS YEAR
May I make a suggestion?
Make it clear like plastic
but use thin plastic wrap instead.
I'm sorry.
So do you cut out comments like those?
Of course.
-"Of course."
-It's too…
-That comment was useless.
-But it can survive
if I put in my two cents.
First, put the wrap on your legs, right?
When he mentioned the plastic wrap,
I considered chiming in.
Can you chime in and save me?
Here's something I thought of.
CAN THE LEGEND SAVE HIM?
First, put on something
more conservative than usual
when you make an appearance,
which turns out to be made of
thin calligraphy paper.
OH, MY GOSH
And it rips when it gets wet.
DIRECTOR HANG-JUN…
It'll melt and disappear.
Calligraphy paper will melt
when they get wet.
And he can have plastic wrap inside.
THANKS TO HANG-JUN,
THE PLASTIC WRAP TALK IS BACK
He saved you.
PHEW
-He's already performing by now.
-Right.
-So maybe next year.
-Next year.
This year, I found the material
in our day-to-day life.
-I see.
-What?
You'll often see it on windows.
WINDOWS?
-Mosquito net?
Did you bring it?
-What is it?
-Wait.
INTENSELY ORANGE NET
Is that a mesh bag for onions?
-It is.
-It's lacy.
SHOCKED
This is the top. What's important is this.
I think I've seen this
on Believe It or Not! type of show.
-And his pants.
-Of course.
It'd make international news briefs.
ENTIRELY MADE OF MESH
-This is the whole outfit?
-Yes.
DAZED…
I'm wearing pants with slits over these,
-so you can see these through them.
-Through the opening.
RELIEVED
So they peek out.
Use them as a mosquito net after the show.
RECYCLABLE AS A NET
-Directors often make pledges, right?
-How cool.
-Yes.
-Pledges for…
HANG-JUN HELD A FREE COFFEE TRUCK EVENT
…the number of admissions.
So if your next project also surpasses
ten million admissions…
-Again?
-You just saw
J. Y. Park's outfit with us, right?
THE MOSQUITO NET REAPPEARS
Why don't you put that on
and go to the WATERBOMB Festival?
He may not be into the festival,
so wear this and give out coffee
in Gwanghwamun Square.
THANK YOU FOR TEN MILLION ADMISSIONS
-Let's do that.
-Okay.
-I'll send it right over at ten million.
-If it happens.
What I'm questioning the most right now
is why J. Y. Park seems
so excited about this.
It's a shame
to let it go to waste after one use.
There's no way it'll hit ten million.
If it does, just attend
a post-screening meet-and-greet.
-And wear that.
-Wearing that?
-That's better than the festival.
-Is the meet-and-greet better?
Not a single person here
is trying to put themselves in my shoes.
THE MALTESE IS ANGRY
I would dance around naked at ten million!
I would even play soccer in that
if I could.
TEASING
I just physically can't.
I see.
Why don't we put that on and cook all day?
THERE'S ZERO DEMAND FOR IT
In that case…
In that case,
-I'll be at the theater in that.
-At the theater. That's fine, right?
HANG-JUN PLEDGES TO DO A FANMEET IN
J. Y. PARK'S OUTFIT AFTER 10M ADMISSIONS
That's sealed.
I want to leave you with one thing.
No, thanks. That's all.
CAN'T TAKE IT BACK
You can't take it back now.
I'll accept my fate.
ACCEPTS IT LIKE A CHILL GUY
Like how Hang-jun has had
Poong in his life,
J. Y. Park claims that he has brought up
one of the chefs here.
-What?
-Don't you produce singers?
-Do you also produce chefs?
-Who?
I've never heard it.
Who's the chef that you brought up?
IT'S SON JONG-WON?
-Really?
-Are you serious?
I don't know how he did it, but great job.
Back when nobody knew him,
when not many people knew of him,
I ate at his restaurant and said,
"Who is this guy?"
"I love this guy."
-And I took his number.
-"I love this guy."
I'm not the type who enjoys fine dining,
but when I went
to his French restaurant,
I knew he was something special.
-He's the only chef I know the number of.
-Really?
Really?
There's no one else.
This was way before
the first season of Culinary Class Wars.
And I told him
to compete in the second season.
That he had to.
Why wouldn't he?
You all may not have known him
if it hadn't been for me.
AMAZING…
WHAT'S HE SAYING?
We brought Jong-won up.
-Yes.
-He was peeling garlic abroad back then.
BACK IN 2016, SAN FRANCISCO…
-He's good at it.
-He is.
-We showed him support.
-It was way back when.
-Was it San Francisco?
-It was.
-You were peeling garlic cloves.
-Back in 2016.
Back when he was peeling peas?
On Cook Representative.
We practically incubated the guy.
I go out and tell people
that I brought him up.
MY SON, JONG-WON?
Our production crew says that.
You brought up what I had brought up.
Is that the case?
Everyone is trying to take the credit.
We need him to admit to this.
-Yes.
-That's true.
Do you agree with any of this?
Recently, I've definitely been hearing
many people say
that they brought me up.
-Yes, right?
-We did.
I believe my mother
was the one who brought me up.
-True.
-So it was your mother.
-It was his mother.
-It was.
-But there is a connection.
-I'm very grateful.
-Wait, what?
-I can't dance.
There's disconcerting information.
-What?
J. Y. Park said he'd send our crew
a picture with information about his body,
and he insisted
that we show it to the chefs
before they start cooking.
-What?
-His body?
-I have to share my order soon, right?
-Yes.
This information
is directly related to that.
A-HA
-Something he can't eat?
-All right.
-Please take a look.
-Okay.
I hear the production crew shrieked
after seeing this.
-They did? Why?
-What?
We haven't seen it yet.
J. Y. PARK'S BODY PORTRAIT
Is this a recent photo?
Yes, I actually only had 9.2% of body fat.
-Yes, "body fat, 9.2%."
-Look at his body fat.
WHAT NOW?
I can't eat carbs
for the next three months.
I would die. I can't live like that.
How will he eat, then?
So you've actually hit
this 9.2% body fat before?
I usually maintain around 12 to 13%,
and recently, I tried going down to that.
AMAZED
I promised my fans
that I'd show them
my best performance at 60,
which is now only five years away.
So I've been getting in shape
to do a great job for the last five years.
It was a promise to his fans.
In some respects,
I did better in my twenties and thirties,
but overall,
I'm in my best physical condition now.
-Compared to your younger days?
-Yes.
I'm way more flexible now too.
Do you suffer from any chronic illnesses?
-Like blood pressure.
-Yes, blood pressure and all.
Nothing.
As expected.
J. Y. PARK AGES IN REVERSE
When you cook for J. Y. Park today,
you must take
his physical condition into consideration.
-You're right. That's not easy.
-That'll probably be his order.
We're about to look into the fridge
of the man who's conditioning himself
until the day he hits 60, J. Y. Park.
-Do you use this with your family?
-Yes.
With my wife and two daughters.
You seem to pay a lot of attention
to maintaining your health.
Is it different from the fridges
in other households?
-It's quite different.
-It is?
-How so?
I once saw on TV
that you had a morning routine…
-Yes, with supplements.
-…of working out and eating.
Have you been keeping that up?
As soon as you wake up?
First, I memorize 20 English words.
YOU'RE STUDYING ENGLISH?
Memorizing 20 English words?
How can you memorize anything
before breakfast?
Your brain wakes up before your body.
My brain wakes up around 1:00 p.m.
After that, I eat breakfast,
stretch, work out,
then practice piano and singing.
Also, he's famous
for his love for organic products.
-You're right.
-The word is out there.
Why do you insist on
using organic products?
The artists signed with my agency
would do something like this
whenever they'd impersonate me
because I had severe atopic eczema.
I'm not supposed to scratch myself,
so I slapped myself instead.
HAD TO SLAP HIMSELF TO HANDLE THE ITCH
I lived like that my whole life,
and one day, I thought,
"Is there really no way?"
So I began to study autoimmune diseases,
and what I found was, in a nutshell,
that I should not let
bad things enter my blood system.
"Organic" just means
they're free of pesticides and chemicals
and have minimal processing.
I tried doing that for three months.
I had severe eczema and hay fever,
which usually come together.
For the first time in 40 years,
I breathed through my nose
in my sleep and woke up in shock.
THAT CAN HAPPEN?
So that can happen?
And it's been 12 years
since I scratched myself.
HIS ORGANIC LIFESTYLE MADE A CHANGE
Food is the best medicine.
That's why you said you were
in your best physical condition now.
-Let's see how organic his fridge is.
-Let's see it.
-I should learn from him.
-Let's look at J. Y. Park's fridge.
I should live like that.
-We're about to begin.
-I should copy him.
The fridge for a family of four,
-we present J. Y. Park's fridge!
-Fridge!
SURPRISED
-There's nothing.
-What's that?
His freezer's empty.
THE FRIDGE IS FULL
-He has nothing in the freezer.
-Barely anything.
It's empty.
I can see that
his fridge must be quite healthy
and even Westernized.
The thing is,
he's not prepared for an emergency.
WHAT EMERGENCY?
He'll have to starve in case of emergency.
Let's take a look from the top. Some eggs.
Organic fertilized egg, free-range.
You must eat a lot of eggs.
After conducting
many experiments on myself,
if I must recommend one perfect food,
it would be eggs.
THAT'S TRUE
However, the chickens must be free-range
and must be fed good feed
in a good environment.
Free-range organic fertilized egg.
ALL EARS
I've always loved them,
and they're good for you too.
So I love dishes
that use eggs as the main ingredient.
I see.
What's your favorite egg dish?
Wrinkly rolled omelet.
KOREAN-STYLE, GOLDEN BROWN
-Overcooked?
-Korean-style rolled omelet.
-That and kimchi-jjigae with saury.
-That's so good.
HE UNEXPECTEDLY LOVES KOREAN FOOD
So eggs are a perfect food.
I see lots of cheese here.
Do you like cheese?
Not really. I only love burrata.
STRONG PREFERENCES
-Burrata with ground pepper.
-That's good.
GOSH
-He's imagining it.
-With ground pepper.
I like to eat that with beef tenderloin
for lunch.
I don't eat a huge breakfast.
I just eat nuts, fruit, and yogurt.
-That's all?
-No big meals.
But I eat a proper lunch.
I only eat within a 6-hour window,
then fast for 18 hours.
Wait.
Do you not eat dinner?
On days that I must eat dinner,
I skip lunch.
THOROUGH CALORIE INTAKE CONTROL
I can dance and work out better
when I'm on an empty stomach.
-I hear you drink oil in the morning.
-Oil?
I take different oils in shot glasses.
-Different kinds?
-Not just one?
No, not just one.
Olive oil is a given.
At times, I take fish oil…
-For omega-3.
-…or olive oil extract.
You're right. These are all organic too.
Even his ground sesame and salt
are organic.
-These are organic too.
-You're right.
Even toasted sesame.
-And ground pepper.
-Ground pepper.
ORGANIC
Organic sesame oil.
Organic green plum extract.
Hang-jun didn't eat fruit,
but you have some, including green grapes.
Blueberries, lemons, and apples.
Do you enjoy fruit?
I only eat them in the morning.
Hang-jun, as we age,
we have to eat fruit for enzymes.
-Right.
-Enzymes in fruit…
-I'll eat some.
-…are important for people.
It works wonders for anti-aging.
-Really?
ACCEPTS THE ADVICE
-But in the morning. It's high in sugar.
-Like berries.
-He's like a professor.
-He is.
The second shelf has
-lots of meat.
-That's more meat than I expected.
Organic whole chicken.
EVEN THAT?
-Anything that isn't organic is banned.
-Off limits.
And this one is antibiotic-free pork.
If I can't find organic products,
I go down to no antibiotics
and eco-friendly ones.
-Pork.
-Yes.
These all exist out there.
We just didn't know.
You have many different pork cuts.
I love pork.
Pork is hands down
my favorite type of meat.
THE BEST KIND OF MEAT
-What's this?
-Brown croaker?
-It's probably a brown croaker.
-It's a brown croaker.
MUST ROTATE THE SCREEN TO FIT
-First time on the show.
-It looks fresh.
That's a really expensive fish.
-A ridged-eye flounder.
-Ridged-eye flounder?
You eat that at home?
ABALONES
How do you eat these? They're huge.
I try to find wild-caught fish
instead of farmed ones.
EVEN SEAFOOD MUST BE WILD-CAUGHT
You have lots of kimchi too.
Green onion kimchi, cabbage kimchi,
mukeunji, water kimchi.
-Do you like kimchi?
-I love them, really.
I've loved it since two decades ago.
I actually used to love Western cuisine.
I see. Western cuisine.
But between 2003 and 2008,
I went to America in an attempt
to sell K-pop to major music labels.
No one would even meet me,
and they didn't know
-where Korea was.
-With Wonder Girls?
I ended up facing
so many upsetting situations.
I'd pack my backpack with 30 CDs
and did my round with music labels,
asking them to have a listen.
But the response wasn't so great,
and I started to miss Korea,
then began my obsession with Korean food.
HE ALSO BEGAN TO MISS KOREAN FOOD
I began to crave them,
and all I had on my mind
was kimchi and pork.
And I began to keep many kinds of kimchi.
-It happens.
-I get it.
Times were pretty tough, and my love
for kimchi and pork began back then.
K-FOOD BECAME HIS COMFORT
Pork and kimchi saved you.
But now,
even last week, the biggest label
in America came here for a meeting.
-The tables have turned.
-Times have changed.
Just last year, we earned more
in America than in Korea.
I can clearly see why he leads
the Presidential Committee
on Popular Culture Exchange.
-Yes, he knows the ins and outs.
-That's why he took it up.
Lots of veggies in the crisper drawer,
and again, organic chives.
-These are all organic.
-Organic spinach.
Do you enjoy vegetables?
-I like them.
-I see.
But for green onions…
I put them in, then take them out later.
-Why?
-Just the aroma?
Yes, I like the aroma.
It tastes weird in my mouth.
HE DOESN'T LIKE THE TEXTURE
But Poong uses a lot of green onion.
A variety of vegetables
that come in different colors
will eliminate a lot
of reactive oxygen species.
So we must eat vegetables
in many different colors
to age slower.
-Was it anthocyanin or something?
-Vibrant colors.
Wait, how long do you want to live?
WE CAN'T EVEN TELL…
Once I show my best performance at 60,
I'll relax a little more.
-After that, will you relax?
-Yes.
Yes, I need to keep my promise
at least until I hit 60.
-It's to keep that.
-He really keeps his promises.
Other than music and organic products,
is there nothing else
you're interested in?
No, not really.
DETACHED
Many others spend money
on expensive cars and watches, but not me.
I put everything into this.
You're kind of like me.
I always splurge on food too.
THAT IS NOT THE SAME!
Was it your idea to use
only organic products for your cafeteria?
I wouldn't be able to face my staff
if only I had good food.
So my agency's cafeteria
is run just like how I would eat.
It's for our employees,
singers, and even trainees.
You know that it's good.
Even for cooking oil, I made sure that
we only used cold-pressed organic oil.
He knows the importance of food.
What's this one?
Organic maple sugar.
When I want to add sweetness,
I choose something
that's the least processed,
and maple sugar is minimally processed.
I feel like
I'm watching a health show right now.
SECRETS TO ORGANIC PRODUCTS
And everything he says
is so easy to understand.
It's captivating too.
My friends would make fun of me
and say people like me
die first in accidents.
MY GOSH
That's a curse.
All of them are unwell now,
and they no longer tease me.
HE PROVED IT HIMSELF
What's this? Tofu noodles?
Those are noodles made with tofu,
so they're much lower in carbs and sugar.
What's the texture like?
-It's not as chewy as regular noodles.
-I see.
But it can pass.
It's free of flour.
My perception of organic products
has changed completely today.
AFTER LISTENING TO THE PROFESSOR
Why am I taking herbal medicine?
I should use good ingredients.
-Yes, eat organic food.
-Yes.
I'm just an organism
while he's organic.
So I think I should choose
organic products when I can.
THE PROFESSOR IS PROUD
In the freezer,
there's rice cake.
Organic rice cake.
You're famous for your love of rice cake
and was nicknamed the Rice Cake Gorilla.
This is one thing you can't give up on.
I brought it so I could have some today.
TO COMMEMORATE HIS VISIT TO THE SHOW
I wanted to eat something
made by excellent chefs like them.
That's all for J. Y. Park's fridge!
A FRIDGE ONLY FILLED WITH ORGANIC PRODUCTS
-That was amazing.
-It was.
He has a lot of love for organic products.
-And we learned a few things, right?
-Yes.
-I want to try copying him.
-We should live like him.
What's important
isn't eating what's good for you.
Just avoid eating what's bad for you.
Right.
But most people think
it's the other way around.
What's important
is not eating what's bad for you
but staying away from those
is the toughest.
It's weird how the food
that's bad for you is all good.
-They taste good.
-They're so good.
You're right.
Alcohol is so delicious, isn't it?
And it makes you feel so happy.
HAPPY
Now, get ready.
Let's find out
what J. Y. Park's orders are.
Here are his orders.
J. Y. Park's orders!
-Peaking at 60.
Peaking at 60.
He's doing all this
-for his performance at 60.
-For that performance.
What are you looking to eat?
Help me maintain this great condition
in the remaining five years
by using sugar and carbs
as little as you can,
and using mostly protein and veggies.
-High protein, low calories.
-Also, I really love eggs,
so please use eggs as the main ingredient.
He wants you to use a lot of eggs.
-The second order.
-The second one.
-Half pork, half kimchi.
Not half sound, half air.
-No. Half pork, half kimchi.
-Half pork, half kimchi.
What are you looking for?
Whenever I return from business trips
to America or any other countries,
I always have to eat
something made with pork and kimchi.
That sounds good.
But I always eat the same thing,
so I wanted something new.
For this order,
you don't have to consider
the calories or carbs.
Something that
makes me feel like I'm in Korea.
-It doesn't have to be organic. The oil--
-It has to be organic.
But carbs are allowed.
No limits on the carbs and the calories.
-Everything you have is organic anyway.
-Yes.
Yong-wook has joined us
since the last episode.
-Do I get the first pick?
-Would you like to go first?
-Why do you seem so rushed?
-I do feel rushed.
I don't think I can do the one with eggs.
-So the pork?
-Pork.
-The pork round?
-If I can choose, yes.
-Half Pork, Half Kimchi.
-All right.
-Hey, Poong.
You're also from the streets.
-I am. Just like that?
-Why don't you face him?
Streets versus streets?
He's a tough one.
-All right. Half Pork, Half Kimchi.
-Half Pork, Half Kimchi.
-Thank you for joining me.
-Okay.
The two have chosen
Half Pork, Half Kimchi,
-which puts Jong-won and Sam up there.
-Jong-won and Sam.
Is that okay?
His fridge looked
-very ideal to me. I'd be happy to join.
-Yes, he's like him.
Sam, you must be confident about this.
Yes, it's a chance to show
my naturalist philosophy again.
Yes, he was originally a naturalist.
To be exact,
a former naturalist chef.
He's the former naturalist chef
who has compromised quite a lot.
Now, the first round.
Let us begin the 15-minute cook-off
between Sam and Jong-won!
The first round, played with ingredients
from J. Y. Park's fridge.
Chef Son Jong-won,
who's currently peaking
thanks to our show,
versus Chef Sam Kim,
who'll take Jong-won down today
and steal that peak from him.
These two have always shown
a great cook-off
whenever they faced each other.
You two have done the cook-off five times,
and Jong-won has
won four times and lost once.
-He won four times?
-Four times?
However, Jong-won is facing a wall
after his ninth win.
He has lost three times in a row,
while trying to get his tenth star.
That's why we still don't have anyone
who has stars in the two digits.
WE HAVE ONE WITH ONLY TWO STARS THOUGH
Will you use Sam
as the sacrifice for the tenth win?
Is that possible?
Sam has been on a roll recently.
He has won many stars
in his sweeping upturn.
Some even say
-he was nicknamed the SO Chef.
-SO Chef.
-Star-Obsessed Chef.
-I didn't make it.
-SO Chef.
He recently became scarier
-because of his thirst for stars.
-True.
-So I'm nervous.
-Right.
He used to only make vegetable stock.
BACK WHEN HE ALWAYS MADE VEGETABLE STOCK
-Only vegetable stock.
-That's how he started out.
Vegetable stock is great,
but to win stars,
I must abandon it from time to time.
-He is the SO Chef.
-He is.
-His canine is getting sharper.
-SO Chef.
I really miss Sam's vegetable stock.
When was the last time we've seen it?
I'll make something similar
-to vegetable stock.
-You will?
-Will you make it?
-He must have a plan.
Jong-won also says
he's confident about this round,
saying he lives on eggs.
-Is this true?
-It's true.
I believe we began having eggs
in the green room
ever since I joined the show.
-That's true.
-We only had ramyeon before.
But when I tried to eat some
before this round, they were all gone.
-Someone else ate them.
-They're popular now.
People add them to ramyeon.
-Was it you?
-It wasn't me!
I only had ramyeon.
-Who was it?
-Who was it, Eun-yeong?
TURNING HIMSELF IN
-It was Ho-young.
-Chef Ho-young.
I ate two and put one in my ramyeon.
I had three.
You're so honest.
I like eggs too.
SNACKS ARE FIRST-COME, FIRST-SERVED
-SO Chef, anything to say about eggs?
-"SO Chef"?
NEW NICKNAME CONFIRMED
J. Y. Park's fridge
is similar to my fridge.
-Is it really?
-Yes.
My son used to have atopic eczema.
Really?
Also, I always eat eggs in the morning,
So it's an ingredient I can handle well.
CHEF SAM'S INGREDIENTS:
EGG, BROWN CROAKER, ABALONE, PROSCIUTTO
SAFFRON, KING OYSTER MUSHROOM,
SPINACH, ASPARAGUS, RADISH, AND MORE
Chef Sam, what are you making?
I'm going to make three dishes.
First, I'll use a whole egg
and make deviled eggs
with mayo from scratch,
then I'll mix it with abalone
and some asparagus.
You'll be able to enjoy
a rich and savory whole egg dish.
Second, I'll make a warm salad
with egg yolks,
by stir-frying mushroom and spinach
and covering it with hollandaise sauce.
He had saffron, so I'll add a bit of that
and make a salad
that brings out the egg yolk flavor.
-Next is the main dish…
-Do you have time?
…which uses egg whites.
I'll make meringue,
top it over the brown croaker,
and steam it together.
So the three dishes will be
a whole-egg dish,
an egg yolk dish,
and finally, an egg white dish.
-It sounds like a course meal.
-That's crazy.
Can he do that in 15 minutes?
CHEF JONG-WON'S INGREDIENTS:
EGG, OCTOPUS, ABALONE, BEEF TENDERLOIN
TOFU NOODLES, GREEK YOGURT,
WATER PARSLEY, RADISH SPROUTS, AND MORE
What are you making, Jong-won?
When J. Y. Park mentioned his peak,
I thought every moment of his career
was a peak and thought it was admirable.
I wanted to express my respect
for the peak of his career,
-so I also prepared three egg dishes.
-You did?
I'm making Korean food
to spread K-food around the world.
-Korean food.
-I'll make a feast…
-…for your hwangap, the 60th birthday.
-A feast?
-His 60th birthday?
-But I thought
a party would suit him better,
so I'll call it the 60th party.
So I'll cook these for his 60th.
-I'll begin with suranchae.
-Suranchae.
It's a dish passed down through
the Gyeongju Choi family for generations.
It's made with a poached egg,
served with sesame seed juice.
I'll also make yukjeon, beef jeon.
-Jeon is a must for a feast, right?
-Beef jeon is delicious.
Lastly, I'll prepare
soft steamed eggs with soy sauce,
which will end your meal on a soft
-and wet note.
-Soft and wet.
Soft and wet. It'll be creamy.
Deliciously.
Cooking is usually the toughest part,
but today, sharing the name was harder.
TRYING HIS BEST
This is how you grow.
Are you sweaty? Why don't you wipe it off?
Yes, I'm getting wet.
He's ready to go.
He's become a TV personality.
It sounds like this will be a tough round.
Now, let us begin the round,
Peaking at 60.
The Star-Obsessed Chef, aka SO Chef,
Chef Sam Kim.
Versus the Egg-Obsessed Chef,
aka EO Chef,
Chef Son Jong-won.
-"EO Chef."
-Eggs and stars.
Who'll help J. Y. Park stay at his peak?
Let the 15-minute cook-off begin!
JYP.
LET'S DO THIS!
EGGS
SAM WILL MAKE THREE DIFFERENT EGG DISHES!
It'll be a fierce round.
HE BEGINS WITH THE BROWN CROAKER!
They're using fish and meat, respectively.
-Brown croaker.
-That's a meaty one.
That's really…
That fish is no joke.
It's huge, isn't it?
It's almost too big.
-Wow.
-It's big.
That brown croaker is insane.
Look now plump the meat is.
It looks so nice.
Who'll finish prepping faster?
He prepped the fish in a flash.
-Fish. Fish stock.
-Are you adding the bones?
-He's making fish bone broth.
-Bone broth.
Brown croaker broth
turns out like beef bone broth.
It's fish,
but it looks like beef bone broth.
Brown croaker broth turns out milky-white,
and it's absolutely delicious.
-Fish bone broth is really good.
-It's the best.
A-HA
That was why he said he'll make
something similar to vegetable stock.
He's prepping the meat already.
It's for beef jeon.
For beef jeon, it's very important
-to make the slices even.
-I see.
-Jong-won is making beef jeon.
-Those look perfect.
I wanted to let J. Y. Park
sound even more tender,
so I'll use tenderloin.
JEEZ…
WHAT WAS THAT?
I'm disappointed.
He's been dying to be funny lately.
He's preparing the beef tenderloin
to make jeon.
1. SALT AND PEPPER THINLY SLICED BEEF
Jong-won seems to be taking the lead.
2. STEAM ABALONE
That's an abalone.
-He's steaming an abalone.
-Steaming an abalone.
-Meringue.
Sam grabs an egg.
-Huh?
-Just the whites?
-You got some yolk in there.
-Some got in.
-It's fine.
-You can't use that.
He can't make meringue with that.
It's impossible to make meringue.
Oh, no!
OH, BOY
It's an emergency.
RETRY
The organic egg!
The organic fertilized egg!
We're sorry, chickens.
J. Y. Park splurged his money
on nothing else but those eggs!
-Gosh, what a waste.
-That's his everything!
MAKING MERINGUE WITH NEW EGGS!
Meringue.
TAPPING
What's Jong-won up to?
I'm mixing eggs and yogurt.
-Yogurt?
-Eggs and yogurt?
He's adding syrup.
3. MIX EGG, YOGURT, MAPLE SYRUP,
GRAIN SYRUP AND STRAIN
He said he'd make steamed eggs,
so is that it?
I'm trying to make "WET" egg pudding.
"WET" egg pudding.
He coated the insides of the bowls
with butter.
POUR TO MAKE PUDDING-LIKE EGGS!
You're making them like pudding.
I guess he'll time them.
He pulled out a timer.
COVER
He'll steam them like that?
There's an abalone inside.
He's going to steam them.
4. BUTTER THE BOWLS,
POUR EGG MIXTURE, AND STEAM
NEXT, POACHING AN EGG!
-The poached egg.
-He'll poach an egg.
The poached egg.
Swirl and poach the egg!
YOU!
He's unfazed.
He's no longer the old Jong-won.
SAM CUTS THE ORGANIC RADISH
SLICED
-What? What's he doing? A radish?
-Is that a radish?
-He's grinding the radish.
-Radish.
Why are you grinding the radish? What for?
Brown croaker.
He topped the radish with brown croaker.
-To steam them?
-He'll steam them together.
That's how he'll steam it?
I'll steam it.
-To steam it? And meringue?
-The meringue is ready.
Meringue? Why?
-Will he put it on top?
-He said he would.
-On top.
-And steam it.
He mixed ground radish with the meringue.
Steamed brown croaker with meringue.
GASP
That's how you do it? That's new.
-Will it get cooked in time?
-Why are you using radish?
-As the support.
-The support.
He doesn't have to eat it, then?
NEXT, THE EGG YOLK DISH!
MINCED GARLIC
He's adding lemon juice.
That lemon.
It's really hard to find organic lemons,
so whenever they're available,
I rake in as many as I can find.
Then I wash them
with organic sanitizing solution,
wrap them in kitchen towels,
and seal them up in a zipper bag.
Those lemons smell
much stronger than you'd expect.
He says it smells strong.
4. MAKE LEMON MAYO
WITH EGG YOLK AND CONDIMENTS
Ten minutes left.
It's been five minutes already.
IN!
CRUNCHY WATER PARSLEY STEMS!
What's that? Long-legged octopus?
Octopus? It looks like it.
-Octopus?
-Octopuses are always a must
for a feast at a nobleman's house.
THAT'S TRUE
So instead of an octopus,
I'll use the long-legged one.
Isn't it too early to have his 60th feast?
6. BLANCH LONG-LEGGED OCTOPUS LEGS
His 60th party.
DONE
PLACE THE BLANCHED WATER PARSLEY
AND OCTOPUS IN ICED WATER!
TIMER FOR THE POACHED EGG!
He's very methodical.
-That looks great.
-The egg got poached perfectly.
-It's as plump as a baby's face.
-The egg got poached.
It looks similar to burrata,
his favorite cheese.
You're right.
He's getting the abalone.
That abalone is nice and plump.
He's using all those for suranchae.
You have around eight minutes left,
about halfway done.
-King oyster mushroom.
-You don't have much time.
-Organic mushroom.
5. COOK KING OYSTER MUSHROOM
IN GARLIC BUTTER
INGREDIENT PREPPING:
1. KING OYSTER MUSHROOM
Sam cooks spinach.
I have a feeling
that he might run out of time.
You have to make hollandaise too.
He has to make the sauce too.
HOLLANDAISE SAUCE MADE WITH EGG YOLKS!
7. STIR EGG YOLK OVER LOW HEAT
Huh?
You have to keep stirring it.
THERE'S SO MUCH TO DO…
He could use an extra pair of hands.
SWITCHING AGAIN
SPINACH
-Spinach?
-Spinach is done.
PREPPING: 2. SPINACH
ASPARAGUS
BUTTER
8. COOK CHOPPED ASPARAGUS IN GARLIC BUTTER
He said he'd make a warm salad.
-You have seven minutes left.
-Seven minutes.
When will he make beef jeon?
JONG-WON HAS A LONG WAY TO GO TOO!
A WHOLE EGG
QUICKLY PREPARING THE EGG WASH!
What's that for?
-Beef jeon.
-For beef jeon.
-Yes, beef jeon.
J. Y. Park knows more
than Hyun-suk.
The two chefs
are extra-focused today.
This is no joke.
They're serious.
Both chefs have to make three dishes.
They have to make all three.
So that's the dish
the Gyeongju Choi family eats.
It's a well-established dish.
7. MAKE SESAME JUICE
What's that? Balsamic vinegar?
He's using organic maple syrup.
8. MAKE MAPLE SOY SAUCE GLAZE
GARLIC
There's no time.
PROSCIUTTO
I think he used vinegar.
OCCASIONALLY WORKS ON
THE HOLLANDAISE SAUCE…
BOILED EGGS
PROSCIUTTO AND FISH BROTH!
-He's mixing something.
-It's the brown croaker broth.
Just the fish broth, no seasoning.
Brown croaker, garlic, and ham.
That hollandaise sauce is the problem.
-Hollandaise.
-It hasn't turned into cream.
-I don't think he added butter.
-I haven't yet.
You didn't, right?
What's he adding?
Melted butter.
Only five minutes left.
It's almost five minutes.
But they both haven't made a single dish.
Right? They should've finished one by now.
-Can they do this?
-No matter how busy you are…
Abalone?
-Abalone.
You're adding abalone now?
He must've forgotten.
-So put it in now?
-He should've done it already.
Did you add saffron?
-I didn't.
-Saffron. Come on. Quickly.
-He had saffron?
-Saffron.
SAFFRON
His mouth is shaped like a square.
Did he pull out the abalone?
No, he didn't do that yet.
He did. It's on the board.
-Sung-ju, why don't you go check?
-Yes?
He boiled it for three seconds.
-Three seconds?
-Really?
Should I go?
-Report to us from the kitchen.
-I think they need much more time.
-Why did he boil that?
-It's already out.
He threw the abalone in
and pulled it right out.
-Barely boiled.
-Is that right?
-The abalone was in there briefly, right?
-It's right.
I have no time.
The abalone went in and came right out.
-"Oh, it's hot."
-It's pretty much raw.
Is it raw?
-You can chop it.
-He looks baffled.
-Wait. It's an emergency.
-It is an emergency.
-It's an emergency.
-No.
-He says it's not.
-Is that okay?
-He's peeling the boiled eggs.
-Boiled eggs.
It got peeled nicely. The boiled egg.
Many people are worried about Sam.
Are we?
JONG-WON STARTS MAKING BEEF JEON
In the egg wash.
9. POWDER AND EGG BEEF, MAKE JEON
-He's making beef jeon.
-Beef jeon!
-Beef jeon.
-It looks good.
Four minutes left.
Four minutes.
-None of the dishes are ready.
-Right?
I guess everything will be ready at once.
It has to be a course meal.
But I don't see
anything that's ready on the counter.
-It's cooked well, but it got smashed.
-The egg! No!
The egg!
-It's for the deviled egg.
-He seems fine.
-Really?
-Yes.
-A stuffed egg.
-You know, like mayo.
-Right. Deviled egg.
Nothing's ready.
-Do you have enough time?
-I doubt it.
You have to finish
one dish a minute starting now.
Otherwise, you can't make it happen.
You need to make three dishes,
so one dish every minute!
You have three minutes,
no, three minutes and 30 seconds!
You have to wake up!
What are you doing?
-This is bad.
-I thought it'd be a course meal.
-It's ready.
-Something's ready.
-Is that okay?
-It's ready.
Deviled egg.
-Deviled egg.
Sam finished something
that looks like a dish.
Can you wipe the dish?
-Sam finished one dish.
-Sam made one.
-Three minutes!
-Three minutes.
Jong-won doesn't have anything ready yet.
-It's an emergency.
-You have under three minutes.
Three minutes. Emergency!
-Emergency.
-In this busy time,
-he's making them the same length.
-Exactly. Look.
The same lengths.
THE EXACT SAME SIZE AS THE CUCUMBER!
He's making the abalone
exactly the same size too.
IN AWE…
Beef jeon is in the making.
Beef jeon.
-It looks great.
-Two and a half minutes.
Two and a half minutes.
-Get the steamed dish out.
-Okay.
-Sam's second dish.
-The second one.
-The second dish, with spinach.
-The second one? Right away?
-Excellent.
-Hollandaise.
Hollandaise? Did it happen?
Hollandaise with saffron.
-He's using it for this dish.
-Wait.
-It's too runny.
-It's just raw egg yolk.
That's just beaten eggs.
-Enough! That's enough!
-Shouldn't it be creamier?
Look, the next one is ready.
Steamed brown croaker! With meringue!
It's the beaten egg for shabu-shabu.
Be quiet.
-Just be quiet.
-I'm just wondering.
He told you to be quiet.
-Be quiet.
-I have to be quiet?
-Sam's mad.
-Is he?
-Be quiet.
-"Be quiet."
I have to be quiet?
-The soup.
-It's an emergency.
Lemon? That looks good.
-You have lots of time.
-I do?
-Let me try this broth.
-Try the broth!
What did he do with this one?
That was SO Chef's doing.
Do you see the star?
Yes, I do see the star!
-Yes, I do see the star!
-You do?
-What is that?
-What's that?
-It tastes subtle and nice.
-Really?
It's just like his old dishes.
-You're done?
-Already?
SAM KIM FINISHES THE CHALLENGE!
Everything's ready.
He finished so suddenly.
Sam's finished.
He sets the tray.
Jong-won.
You have one minute left!
-Jong-won, 50 seconds.
-I wonder what the poached egg is like.
Poached eggs are great for pockets.
-Gosh…
-Poached and pockets.
He's trying to be funny
with 40 seconds left.
He has time to throw a joke!
I HAVE TWO MORE TO GO!
SECOND DISH, STEAMED EGGS!
It must be hot!
-It's hot.
-It has to be hot.
Steamed eggs are ready.
-Beef jeon.
-Shouldn't he cut it?
-Twenty seconds!
-Beef jeon is ready.
-Emergency.
-It's hot!
They look great.
-They look good.
-Just like that?
-Like that?
-He tops it with soy sauce.
I mixed maple syrup and soy sauce.
-It's a Koreanized sauce.
-Eight. Seven.
-Six.
-Five.
-Four.
-Three.
PLATING THE BEEF JEON!
13. TOP BEEF JEON WITH RADISH SPROUTS
-Time's up!
-Jong-won is done too.
Jong-won is done too.
CHALLENGE COMPLETE!
6 DISHES WERE FINISHED
IN THE LAST 3 MINUTES!
Everything's ready.
LOSING HIS MIND
Isn't this fun?
So many things happen within ten seconds.
Everything came out within three minutes.
They managed to finish all three
within the last three minutes.
That's one dish per minute.
THE DISHES TO HELP HIM HIT HIS PEAK
-The Western dishes.
-This is the Premier League.
IN AWE…
THE TWO CHEFS PUT ON
THE BEST COOK-OFF EVER!
-I don't remember anything.
-I blanked out.
And now,
both chefs have finished
making these meals for J. Y. Park.
These meals will
put him right on the peak.
Director Yong-wook,
did you also enjoy the journey?
He looked as if
he would get a heart attack soon.
I am
deeply regretting the moment
I got the offer on the phone.
Why was I so excited? Why was I so happy?
I'm looking forward to seeing your round.
All right.
Chef Sam finished first,
so please try his meal,
All I See Is Stars, Stars.
THREE-COURSE EGG MEAL
DEVILED EGG
STEAMED BROWN CROAKER WITH MERINGUE
HOLLANDAISE SALAD
YAY
It's my first time
seeing that phone in person.
Try the deviled egg first.
Then, the egg yolk dish,
and finish with the egg white dish.
1. WHOLE EGG, 2. EGG YOLK, 3. EGG WHITE
Squeeze just a little bit of it.
A DASH OF LEMON JUICE ON THE DEVILED EGG
CURIOUS
I suggest that you eat it
with a lot of asparagus.
It does look quite healthy.
I think it suits him very well.
This will help you live a year longer.
He's trying to peak at 60.
WHAT WILL IT TASTE LIKE?
GOSH…
What's it like?
It's so classy.
It's so classy for something
that he made in just 15 minutes.
Secondly,
-I can taste his pride.
-Pride?
-You can taste his pride?
-His pride?
He brought out the original flavors
of egg, abalone, and asparagus.
-It's such a natural dish.
-The natural flavors.
I love dishes like these.
I love it when the dish is like,
"It's me, Sam Kim."
IT'S ME, SAM KIM
Poong was sitting here screaming…
-Right?
-…so he had to cook in the chaos,
but he still remained classy.
But there's one thing. In musical terms,
it's missing some bass.
Some bass?
I want to raise the EQ for bass.
-When the bass is weak, it means…
-Bass be…
LISTEN
UNSTOPPABLE POONGDOZER
Please control yourself.
-He's trying to eat.
-This is a classy show.
-I'm sorry.
-The legends are trying to eat.
I thought you needed a clown. I'm sorry.
You would've been locked up last week.
RIGHT BEHIND BARS
A pinch of salt would've fixed it.
-You're right. It must be the seasoning.
-It's the seasoning.
-Probably.
-It probably is.
Salt does the heavy lifting for food,
so he should've added some.
-That would've helped.
-Salt.
I kind of want to cook for him.
Me too.
-You too?
-Yes.
I wanted you to eat the whole egg as is
to taste the difference
between the yolk and the white after.
So I didn't season it heavily.
-He did it intentionally.
-It's the base.
-The bass will get louder as you go.
-The second one.
-It's the egg yolk sauce.
-Try the egg yolk.
-The first one was a whole egg.
-It's like carbonara.
Now, the charm of egg yolks.
TAKING A BIG BITE
Will it charm its way to him?
It's as if
we're at a hi-fi listening shop.
SAVORING THE FOOD LIKE MUSIC
Will he make up for the first dish?
It's shockingly classy.
Also, as I've mentioned before,
it's so important for me
to see the person behind the dish,
and I can see it completely.
I love that for this dish.
-You can see Sam in it?
-It's that classy?
His face, gestures,
and expressions are all in here.
I love it.
THE DISH IS LIKE HIS OTHER SELF
And there's a bit more bass than before.
But I still want
to raise the EQ a little more.
GOSH…
-Why are you so excited?
-He still needed more.
That one is the brown croaker,
cooked with meringue.
Try the meringue, the fish,
and the broth altogether.
-It's made with fish bones, right?
-Yes, I made it with fish bones.
-This one must have the bass.
-Bass.
-The bass.
-It has to be here.
-Ready to dance?
-Will he hit him with the bass at the end?
Was that why the first two were weaker?
SCOOPS A BIG BITE
WILL HE FIND THE BASS?
-The bass.
-Thump.
You're acting up a lot today.
DOESN'T CARE AND CONTINUES TO PLAY
Is the fish cooked well?
Gosh, it's perfect. The doneness…
The quality is just unbelievable,
and I'm into these things.
He doesn't compromise
the flavor of the ingredients.
I can taste the fish, the mushroom,
and everything on its own.
It's very sophisticated,
and really delicious.
-Right?
-That's Sam's style too.
He's not into dishes
that are too strong or deep.
This is taking the concept of balance
to its pinnacle.
It shows what balance is.
He had a brown croaker,
so he picked out the ingredients
that will not go against the dish.
THE STEAMED FISH HAS NO DOWNSIDE
-Next, Chef Jong-won's meal.
-Jong-won's meal.
BEEF JEON
SURANCHAE
STEAMED EGG
CHEF SON JONG-WON'S DON'T LEAVE ME, EGG
First, break the poached egg.
I made sesame juice
by blending sesame seeds with farro milk.
-Farro.
-A meal for Nobleman Park's 60th birthday.
It's a dish that originated
from the Gyeongju Choi family.
So I wanted to serve it at the feast
for the leader of JYP Entertainment.
It's called suranchae.
Poached egg with some seafood.
A BIG BITE
-I wonder what it's like.
-What's his dish like?
CURIOUS
Sam's dish just now
felt like the sound was evenly spread
from the mid-range to the high range.
But in this, the poached egg
comes through clearly in the mid-range.
It hits you in the middle.
It definitely brings out
the savory egg flavor.
This poached egg does have a hold on me.
It would've been great
if the sauce had a bit more low-mid range.
Actually,
I lowered the EQ
and made the appetizer bland on purpose.
IT WAS INTENTIONAL
You made an acoustic track.
-Unplugged. It's an unplugged dish.
-Unplugged!
JOINING HIS SHENANIGANS
What's next?
Beef jeon. And eggs are a must
when you make jeon.
Also, it's usually served
with seasoned green onion,
but instead, I topped it
with lightly seasoned radish sprouts.
The important thing is for the egg
to hit him with the savory flavor.
PICKS UP THE WHOLE THING
AND INTO HIS MOUTH
He even eats like an expert.
AN EXPERT
And he's savoring it.
I believe really good cooks
are the ones who make
great dishes with tenderloin.
The seasoning is perfect.
It must be seasoned perfectly.
Does it hit you with some bass?
-Yes.
-It's the seasoning.
-It was the seasoning.
-The salt.
-He needed salt.
-It was salt.
Salt brings out the flavor
of the dish itself.
-Yes.
-It doesn't just make it saltier.
The bass of cooking
-is salt.
-That's why.
That's why you keep salting your food,
even when you don't have time.
THE EXPERT OF SALT
The thickness of the tenderloin
is perfection.
-It must be perfect.
-Is it even?
It would've been worse
if it were any thicker or thinner.
It seemed very important.
-What's this?
-Use the small spoon.
-The small spoon.
-It's on the side.
-Steamed egg.
-I mixed yogurt and egg,
and topped it with a mix
of maple syrup and soy sauce.
-It was organic maple syrup too.
-A "WET" dish.
-It's creamy and "WET."
-It's Japanese-style, right?
It'll feel like pudding.
-Like pudding.
-Caramel pudding.
Steamed eggs in Japan
remind me of pudding.
AMAZED…
DEEPLY IN AWE
That was almost half air, half eggs.
Right?
-The sweetness.
-It was the sweetness.
It was the sweetness.
HE LIKES HIS FOOD SWEET AND SALTY…
-And saltiness.
-He has a sweet tooth!
-My gosh.
-What about last week?
-He's been holding himself back.
-It the sweetness?
It almost doesn't mix well.
The syrup, the soy sauce,
and the savoriness of the egg don't mix,
but there's a harmony.
A harmony within incongruity.
Even in music,
dissonance can sometimes sound cooler.
You're right.
Chef Hyun-suk brings up music now.
This is why he sings wedding songs!
He's an expert wedding singer.
You should sing a song
for his 60th party too!
PLAYING MUSIC HIMSELF
You're going to get punched.
-He'll punch you.
-Go on, and I'll punch you.
It's time to find out
the decision J. Y. Park made.
Press one for Son Jong-won
and two for Sam Kim.
-It's tough.
-This will be fun.
Please make your decision
and push the button!
He pushed one.
-The legends choose quickly.
-They do.
It's because they must
always decide quickly.
Let's find out the result.
Show us!
They had to make egg dishes
to help him peak.
Will Sam, who's looking to
get revenge on Jong-won,
take his victory?
Or will Jong-won defeat Sam
and finally reach his tenth victory?
Who did J. Y. Park choose?
-A dish to let him peak at 60!
-Which one is it?
The egg dishes!
SON JONG-WON WINS
It was Jong-won.
CHEF SON JONG-WON'S
DON'T LEAVE ME, EGG WINS
-Great work.
-It was Jong-won.
Chef Jong-won was chosen.
Both were immensely high in quality,
but Chef Jong-won was bolder.
The difference was that he chose
to have more ups and downs.
-He finally reaches two digits
-Two digits.
-with ten wins.
-Ten wins.
-Let's hear from him.
-Actually,
"Don't Leave Me" was released in 1994,
and I was often comforted
while listening to that song.
I was in fourth grade.
-Comforted?
-A kid needed to be comforted?
-He'd get scolded by his mom.
-School's tough too.
Life is tough at that age.
And studying with a tutor.
The 11-year-old Jong-won
was often comforted by his song.
It was such an honor
to sing this dish's name before you.
Please put a star on Chef Jong-won!
-Great job.
It goes right above his name tag.
This is Jong-won's tenth star,
making him the sole first place!
JONG-WON TAKES HIS 10TH STAR
Jong-won becomes the sole first place.
This is the second round of cook-off
played with J. Y. Park's ingredients.
SUF.
Street Unorthodox Fighter.
HIGH EXPECTATIONS
The meat expert
who trained in a plastic greenhouse,
Director Yoo Yong-wook,
is against the man who's been
picking up skills from chefs for 13 years,
the master freeloader,
Webtoon Artist Kim Poong.
Director Yong-wook finally stands
in the Chef & My Fridge kitchen.
How do you feel?
I'm worried,
not sure if I'll do a good job,
and I don't know if going against Poong
was the right choice.
My head is full.
WELCOME TO THE KIM POONG ERA
-I saw you using grills on CCW2.
-Yes.
Did you bring one today?
I brought a special one, actually,
to show how determined I am.
-Is there a story?
-It's my first grill, bought back in 1995.
-It's the same age as me.
-Your very first grill?
You bought that in 1995?
I was in third grade,
so it was my dad, not me.
-I was ten years old back then.
-You were ten.
-It's so special.
-The handles used to be made of wood.
I can see that.
The top handle came off,
so I had it fixed with metal.
-That's cool.
-I made my first grilled meat using this.
-Story is very important.
-Of course, it is.
YONG-WOOK TAKES THE LEAD WITH HIS STORY
I also brought
something my father made,
my body.
So I'll do my best too.
-That's everyone's case.
-He's not lying.
The body my dad has made is different.
Don't be so cheeky
and talk when it's your turn.
It's my first time
seeing him at a shoot
for Chef & My Fridge,
and he acts like
he's getting hunted down.
-You caught on to that.
-He's too rushed.
It's as if he's being hunted down
by the laughter hunter.
I'm seeing his new side today.
DIRECTOR YONG-WOOK'S INGREDIENTS:
PORK BELLY, PORK NECK, KIMCHI
TOFU NOODLES, SESAME, PEANUT,
CASHEW NUT SPREAD, MAPLE SUGAR, AND MORE
Director Yong-wook,
tell us about your dish.
The dish I'll be making is
-SeYP.
-SeYP?
-Like JYP?
-JYP?
-Not JYP, but SeYP?
-SeYP.
The way I cook requires fire and smoke,
but J. Y. Park's fridge didn't have
anything I could make smoke with.
I will use charcoal and whatnot,
but I did find organic sesame seeds.
So I'll use that
and add an aroma of sesame.
AMAZED
You said
you'd go abroad to spread
K-culture and K-pop,
and you always had
kimchi and pork when you returned.
I wanted to cook pork
and let you wrap it with kimchi,
just like how I thought
I should embrace you.
-By wrapping?
-By wrapping it around.
-That story.
-Embrace him in the arms of pork.
I'll create smoke with sesame seeds
and embrace him with that first.
I would say sesame seeds
have the Korean aroma.
TOUCHED
It'll be a savory hug.
-Yes, right?
-Savory and nutty.
WEBTOON ARTIST POONG'S INGREDIENTS:
PORK BELLY, PORK NECK, KIMCHI
TTEOKBOKKI TTEOK, POTATO, MAPLE SYRUP,
GRAIN SYRUP, KETCHUP, SESAME OIL
As a long-time fan of J. Y. Park,
when I saw his pink plastic pants
from last year's WATERBOMB Festival,
I was deeply inspired.
I will use food ingredients
to make plastic pants.
Plastic pants? How?
Plastic pants with food?
Can he eat them?
-He can.
-He can eat them.
Gosh, this is…
-Yes.
-They'll be organic plastic pants.
-It'll be story versus theme.
-Story versus theme.
Also, you had
your favorite food, rice cake,
so I'll do whatever it takes
to use it somehow.
HAPPY RICE CAKE GORILLA
-And now,
-Whoa. We're starting now?
…let us begin
the Half Pork, Half Kimchi round
-for J. Y. Park.
-Stay calm.
Lights, please.
Timer, please.
HALF PORK, HALF KIMCHI ROUND BEGINS!
THE GATEKEEPER AWAKENS
My gosh!
-You got this!
-It won't be easy.
ARGH!
I will turn you into a lump of charcoal!
Okay. I got this.
Here to gift J. Y. Park
the best plastic pants of his life,
Webtoon Artist Kim Poong.
THE DANCE IS ON THE HOUSE
THE UNWANTED 2ND LIVE PERFORMANCE
Here to rip Poong's plastic pants in half
and own Chef & My Fridge,
Director Yoo Yong-wook.
Unorthodox versus unorthodox.
Street versus street.
Who's going to be the winner?
Let the 15-minute cook-off begin!
Begin!
THE UNORTHODOX ROUND BEGINS
GREEN ONION
This is the fun kind of cook-off.
I knew it.
AS ALWAYS, POONG'S CHILI OIL
He doesn't like to eat green onion,
so I'll add a lot of aroma into the oil.
LET'S GO!
Let's go!
STRAIGHT TO THE GRILL!
PERILLA OIL
Right away, sesame oil.
-He's using oil?
-Yes.
Director Yong-wook
is pan-frying over the charcoal.
Is he?
-I see.
-There's a pan over the grill.
PEANUTS
Peanuts?
1. GRIND PEANUTS AND OLIVE OIL
TO MAKE PEANUT SPREAD
Are those peanuts?
Yes, he's grinding them with oil.
Okay. The spread.
-What's that?
-Peanut butter.
-Cashew nut spread.
-He'll create smoke with that?
-In a blender?
No, I think that's the sauce.
How will you make smoke with sesame seeds?
Sesame seeds are rich in fat,
so I'm sure the smoke will be different.
It smells different
when there's fat in it.
And he's an expert in that area.
Next, kimchi juice.
-Kimchi?
-He's adding kimchi juice.
1. STRAIN KIMCHI JUICE THROUGH CHEESECLOTH
He's making a flour batter
with kimchi juice.
For the color? Are you making the pants?
-I am.
-The pink pants?
He's already making the pink pants.
-Yes.
-Pink.
Pink pants with kimchi juice?
-Where did he learn that?
-That must be starch.
That's the only way
the batter will turn clear.
You're right.
It's a mix of starch and flour.
There's a technique in Western cuisine
called crystal potato,
where you use starch
to make potato transparent.
TRANSPARENT GARNISH
MADE WITH POTATO STARCH
-He's using that technique?
-Starch turns clear when cooked.
He's rubbing something already.
-Butter.
-Butter?
-Is that for the pants?
-Yes.
Yes, I'll pour the starch into this.
-You steam starch water and do that.
-Like a sheet.
It's been three minutes.
You can probably see
hints of powder, right?
That's because he didn't strain it.
It shows how unorthodox he is.
FIERCE CRITICISM
Don't dismiss the cook
from the streets too much.
If he were a chef,
he would've strained it for a few seconds.
But he still has those lumps.
So Poong has a lot more to learn.
He's covering it with a wrap.
-It'll stick.
-It got stuck.
It got stuck! It's not supposed to stick!
I was so stressed out
whenever he did something like that!
-It's stuck!
-All right.
MIMICS THE POONGDOZER
GETTING A TASTE OF HIS OWN MEDICINE…
-Are you mimicking him?
-It's so annoying when he does this.
FIRST, INTO THE MICROWAVE!
-He grabs kimchi.
-Kimchi.
Yong-wook pulls out napa cabbage kimchi.
He's using the grill.
Is that pork neck?
Yes, I put pork neck on the grill.
And then…
-Sesame seeds are going in.
-He's raising the heat too.
POURING
SESAME SEEDS GO INTO THE FIRE!
I think he's creating smoke.
So smoke comes out
when sesame seeds go into charcoal.
It's rich in fat,
so it creates a lot of smoke.
-It does.
-It's making a lot.
You can create that much smoke
with sesame seeds.
-As they burn.
-Yes.
POTATO
MINCED GARLIC
Minced garlic.
-Pepper.
-One pepper.
And meat.
-And pork neck.
-It looks good.
-Cooking wine.
-Cooking wine. Soy sauce.
-Ten minutes.
-Kimchi!
ADDS KIMCHI TO THE BLENDER TOO!
He's grinding meat with kimchi.
You're grinding pork and kimchi together?
They don't look like pork and kimchi now.
He ground everything up.
Nine minutes.
Yong-wook looks surprised.
-Nine minutes!
-You might want to move a bit faster.
Wow.
You're losing time while chanting, "Wow."
3. MIX CONDIMENTS AND MAKE SEASONING
He's someone who can
cook barbecue even for 20 hours.
OPENING THE LID
He opens the grill lid.
The meat doesn't look too cooked.
-It's okay.
-Is he embracing it with smoke?
-Pork neck.
-He's going to marinade it.
-You're right.
-It looks nicely cooked at the bottom.
I hope the smoky flavor lasts
until he tries the dish,
but I'm not sure if it'll prevail
with the soy sauce marinade.
He's saying smoking
is unnecessary with soy sauce.
And next, some starch.
The mixture.
MIXING WITH THE GROUND FILLING
It looks like kimchi mandu,
dumplings with kimchi.
FIDDLING AND MAKING A SHAPE…
What are you…
What are you making?
-And now…
-Darn it.
-You don't have time.
-He just said, "Darn it."
Poong is going, "Darn it."
Something isn't going well.
What are you making?
They're like meatballs with kimchi.
I think those are the legs
that'll put on the pants.
-Those are the legs?
-They are.
LOOK AT THOSE DETAILS
BIPED
Aren't I right?
He's making plastic pants,
so the filling must be the legs.
So will it be three-dimensional?
-It's in 3D.
J. Y. Park's legs are getting cooked.
IT SOUNDS RATHER GRUESOME
He's always improving.
HIS DEPTH IMPROVES FROM DAY TO DAY
Last time, he made a dinosaur.
He made a T-Rex.
And made it stand?
-No, like this. In 2D.
-It's a shock.
And then…
OPENING THE LID AGAIN
I don't think the meat will cook in time.
Mine?
-No, they will.
-Stay confident.
Will the temperature rise later?
It will get hotter like an oven.
But the grill isn't as hot as you think…
WHAT ABOUT PORK BELLY?
So he's not using the pork belly?
-He just used its fat.
-Just to cook the kimchi?
GRILLING JUST KIMCHI
It tastes delicious
when it's cooked in pork fat.
There's lots of grease in the kimchi now,
both perilla oil and lard.
He cooked kimchi
as he melted the pork belly fat.
I see. But he's not using
the pork belly itself.
Five minutes and forty seconds.
-Five minutes and forty seconds.
-Hurry.
REMOVING THE GRILL IN THE CENTER!
It's Yong-wook's first time here,
but he hears everything
and can even respond.
I guess he can hear us.
Gosh.
Sesame seeds.
WHAT'S THIS MACHINE?
That's a smoking gun!
-What's that?
-You're putting that in there?
It's a Western cuisine technique,
smoke injection.
You can add the smoky aroma
without having to put the food
directly over the charcoal.
Because that'll burn.
4. MIX TOFU NOODLES WITH ANCHOVY AEKJEOT,
VICTORY ONION SAUCE, PERILLA OIL, GARLIC
PREPARING SEASONED TOFU NOODLES TOO!
THE GROUND FILLING
THE REMAINDER GOES INTO ANOTHER PAN!
-Maple syrup.
-Maple syrup?
-What is that?
-Maple syrup goes in that?
-With kimchi?
-Even honey? That's too sweet.
-It's grain syrup.
SQUEEZE
That's too much.
That looks way too sweet.
What's he trying to do?
3. BOIL FILLING WITH MAPLE SYRUP,
GRAIN SYRUP, CHILI OIL, AND WATER
He's using tteokbokki rice cake.
Poong chops tteok.
J. Y. Park will love that flavor.
Now, turn it over.
-Are those burnt?
-They aren't!
-They weren't red, but black!
-Maillard reaction.
-They're burnt? He burnt those?
-No!
-It's the Maillard reaction. It's fine.
-He's making black pants.
I can't believe they're totally charred.
HIS LEGS ARE QUITE TANNED…
Please report from the kitchen, Jung-hwan!
His pants are burnt.
Damn it.
-They're burnt.
-Reduce the heat.
-No, I got this.
-So? Did it work?
-It did. I got this.
-No, right?
It doesn't look ready yet.
I can do this.
FIRST, REMOVE THE PLASTIC WRAP
-The pants.
-Will this become the pants?
CLOSE-UP INSPECTION
J. Y. Park, I'm sorry,
but you can't wear these pants.
What do you mean? They're fine.
Did you burn them because he's tanned?
YOU'RE SO HARSH…
Water parsley.
WATER PARSLEY & BEAN SPROUTS
INTO A STRAINER
ALSO COOKED OVER THE CHARCOAL FIRE
He's smoking
water parsley and bean sprouts too.
He's also smoking
water parsley and bean sprouts?
You've managed the grill very well.
This is the grill that made him.
That's how he adds the smoky aroma.
He's doing everything on the grill.
He's cooking water parsley
and bean sprouts on the grill.
-Ketchup?
-Ketchup. Yes, whatever.
Just add some.
-Sesame oil?
-Sesame oil.
SESAME OIL
And the pants… I'll leave them here.
-It's hot. Damn it.
-It's hot?
-It's hot!
-He's going, "Damn it!"
These legs.
-"Give me back my legs."
-I got no time.
BUT I HAVE MY LEGS…
Damn it. Whatever!
He's suddenly adding ramyeon soup base!
That's too much.
-A mistake.
-That's too salty.
MORE WATER AFTER ADDING RAMYEON SOUP BASE
Poong pours ramyeon soup base in!
He's never been properly trained.
-Can you add a spoon of Greek yogurt?
-Where?
-Where? Here?
-Yes.
And a spoon of peanut spread.
THE PEANUT SPREAD HE HAD MADE
SMOKED VEGGIES, OUT
WHAT'S NEXT?
TOFU NOODLES GO INTO THE CHARCOAL FIRE!
It's chaotic over here,
with the smoke and all.
-Three minutes.
-The smoke!
-That's a lot of smoke.
-It feels like a campground!
MIXING WHILE WATCHING
DRAWING HIS ATTENTION
He embraces it with smoke.
Even the noodles.
EVEN TOFU NOODLES ARE SMOKED
AFTER THE VEGGIES
-Even the tofu noodles.
-After seasoning them.
I see why life has hit him hard
on the face.
He had to deal with the smoke.
Two minutes and forty seconds!
Wait.
WHAT'S POONG UP TO NOW?
PICKING…
Darn it!
PEELING THE PLASTIC PANTS
-The plastic pants!
-The plastic!
LAUGHING OUT LOUD
-The JYPink pants!
-Yes!
-Don't let it rip!
-Careful!
HOW WILL IT GO?
-JYPink.
-The pants.
-The plastic!
-Don't let it rip!
HE PULLED IT OFF!
PERFECT!
KIM POONG MADE IT HAPPEN
Put these on it.
He's making cuts to turn this into pants.
He's a tailor.
-How can this turn into pants?
-This isn't a tailor's shop.
-He'll wrap them up.
-How will you make the pants?
Wait, what will you do with the legs?
-Wait. I can do this.
-The legs are almost…
I can do this.
FOLDING THE PLASTIC DOUGH…
Please! The deity of Chef & My Fridge!
Please be our witness!
ALL HE CAN DO IS PRAY
This is a difficult time for us, everyone!
We seriously need high ratings!
OH, THIS IS HILARIOUS…
NO, IT'S REALLY NOT…
-I see the legs.
-It's done!
THE BIRTH OF THE PLASTIC PANTS
-I see the legs.
-It's done!
-What is that?
-They're pants.
What is that?
MOVED…
THE MOST DEEPLY MOVED…
UNBELIEVABLE…
TANNED LEGS WEARING PINK PLASTIC PANTS
BLACKPINK AT HOME
I can do this. I got this.
I did it. I got it.
AUTOMATICALLY BOWING IN AWE…
I did it.
I SHALL WEAR IT TO THE WATERBOMB FESTIVAL…
This is something only he can make.
-Like the pants aunties like to wear!
-It's not so bad.
Gosh.
-Is this the mixture?
-Yes.
PLATING THE PEANUT SAUCE
CHOPPING GARLIC
CUTTING CHANGNANJEOT,
SALTED POLLACK INTESTINES
CHOPPING VICTORY ONION
TOP EVERYTHING ON THE PEANUT SAUCE
Director Yong-wook is smoking
every single item
he's making for the dish.
-Everything?
-Every single item.
He's cooking everything on the grill.
He's embracing the food with smoke.
REMOVING THE KIMCHI STALK
One minute!
-Taste it first.
-Butter.
I can hear them scream.
-It's chaotic.
-I got this.
His food is almost ready.
PLATING THE KIMCHI AS WELL
IN A HASTE
-I got this!
-Ten seconds?
You both have to wrap up.
ONLY 40 SECONDS REMAIN!
The pants!
It's time to finish.
-What's he adding on the plate?
-It looks like a murder scene.
PLATING THE SAUCE AROUND THE LEGS
-I got it.
-J. Y. Park doesn't look so thrilled.
-It's too gory.
-I can do this.
"Give me back my legs!"
IT'S LOOKING MORE AND MORE CONVOLUTED
-I can do this!
-Give me back my legs!
SMOKED VEGGIES ON TOP OF THE TOFU NOODLES
-I can do this.
-Give me my legs.
-Ten seconds.
-Ten seconds!
THE COUNTDOWN
YOO YONG-WOOK FINISHES SEYP FIRST!
-Yong-wook is done!
-Poong?
Poong is done too.
TURNING IN THE PANTS YOU'RE WEARING,
THOSE SHOULD'VE BEEN MINE
THEY BOTH FINISHED IN TIME
Gosh.
I've always wondered
why everyone sweat like a pig.
Everyone is sweating today.
Those pants are too hilarious.
Those pants are steaming.
THE DISHES SHOOT THROUGH THE SMOKE
They finished with two seconds left.
CRACKING UP
-Gosh.
-The pink pants.
SIMPLY AMAZED
-He had the idea and made it happen.
-These look like real pants.
PLEASED
And now,
both Half Pork, Half Kimchi dishes
have been made for J. Y. Park.
AMAZED
The fight between the unorthodox.
One of them emitted lots of smoke,
-And Poong…
-No! It's not burnt!
It's much more interesting
to see ordinary people fight
instead of professional fighters.
TOTALLY AGREES
Any thoughts after your first cook-off?
I have so much respect for everyone.
HE EXPERIENCED THE LIMIT OF 15 MINUTES
But you also did it. Great job.
Yong-wook finished first,
so please try SeYP first.
PORK NECK, KIMCHI, AND TOFU NOODLES
FULL OF SESAME AROMA
PEANUT SAUCE TO AMPLIFY THE NUTTINESS
DIRECTOR YOO YONG-WOOK'S SEYP
-Did you prepare a performance beforehand?
-Yes.
I brought the lid
because I always open it for my guests.
If it's all right,
may I fill it with smoke?
You can do that? Of course.
You should embrace him.
-It's to embrace him with smoke.
-To embrace him with smoke.
Sesame-scented smoke.
THE SMOKING GUN REAPPEARS
SETTING THE PRE-FILLED SESAME
ON FIRE
His identity truly lies in smoke.
-It smells like…
-Does it smell like sesame?
SMELLS LIKE NUTTY SESAME SEEDS
I feel like I'm at a mill.
-That nutty smell.
-It smells nutty.
-It smells very rich, like sesame.
-It smells so nutty.
-I'll stop here.
-That's all.
Let me open it and release the smoke.
OPENING THE DOME
TA-DA
AMAZED
ALREADY CAPTURES ATTENTION
He seizes his lead.
It smells so good.
Time to try the pork neck.
This is
the golden trio,
bean sprouts, kimchi, and pork.
THAT'S SO TRUE
But how will it change through smoking?
-I've had this often at home.
-Of course.
First, the meat.
FIRST, THE PORK NECK
What's it like
when Director Yong-wook makes it?
GASP
HE CAN'T HIDE HIS REAL RESPONSE
That was a real response.
-His face.
-He's bewitched.
SPEECHLESS
How did you create this texture?
How is it different?
The firmness is…
It's not like I've never had pork before.
The chewy, firm texture is inexplicable.
The difference is immense.
I'm so curious.
EXHILARATED
KIMCHI, WHAT WILL I DO WITH YOU?
He's finally feeling it once again.
Gosh. Oh, boy.
What about the other stuff?
GOSH! THE KIMCHI!
WHAT'S IT LIKE?
How does kimchi taste like this?
He just had kimchi.
-He grilled it over the open fire.
-Yes, over charcoal.
I cooked it in perilla oil and lard.
PRE-COOKED IN TWO DIFFERENT GREASE
AND THEN COOKED OVER CHARCOAL ONCE AGAIN
Pork's flavor has seeped into kimchi,
which brought out its flavor even more.
MY GOSH!
ENDLESSLY AMAZED
-He has touched him deeply.
-That was cooked over the fire too.
Water parsley and what?
-And bean sprouts.
-You cooked it over the open fire.
GOING SEMICONSCIOUS
He was hit three times in a row.
FEELING DIZZY AFTER THREE SMOKY PUNCHES
Gosh.
I want all of you to try this. What now?
I can't find words to describe this dish.
-Noodles, water parsley, bean sprouts.
-Yes.
It's like, "Do you like pork?"
"Then I'll end you with pork."
"What about kimchi?
I'll finish you with that too."
-I'm curious.
-"Finish"?
It's like, "Pork!"
"Kimchi!"
THE MOST EXTREME FLAVORS
I want some.
-The sauce.
-What about the sauce?
-Do I need it?
-He smoked it too.
IT'S ALREADY SO GOOD
I prepared it like jeotgal or jang.
TASTING A SPOONFUL
GOSH… WHAT IS THIS?
-Full marks?
-Is the sauce good too?
Can you smell
the sesame smoke in that too?
-He injected smoke into the sauce.
-He likes the smoky flavor.
Gosh.
All three together.
-The three.
-Try the three together.
PORK NECK, KIMCHI, TOFU NOODLES
IN ONE BIG BITE
-This is what's therapeutic to him.
-Of course.
He always missed pork and kimchi
whenever he came back
from his K-pop business trips.
Right?
-Wow.
THE TUBBY TWINS LIVE VICARIOUSLY
THE SEYP THERAPY
IT'S DRIVING ME NUTS
Gosh.
TOO MOVED TO MOVE
He looks way too moved
with grease all over his lips.
He must've loved strong flavors.
He must have.
-But because of his promise to the fans…
-He held himself back.
-He held it back to perform.
-Look how much he likes it.
This dish
deserves full marks.
-Emergency.
-Full marks?
GASP…
-Emergency, pants.
-We can see it on his face.
It gets full marks as one whole dish,
but also as three different,
distinct dishes too.
You did it, Director Yong-wook.
Why don't you whisper, "SeYP,"
back at him?
ANTICIPATION
SeYP.
THE BEST COMPLIMENT
I want everyone to try it.
What about the pants?
-What about the pants?
-Poong seems anxious.
Poor pants…
The dish Poong made,
The Pants You're Wearing,
Those Should've Been Mine.
PORK AND RICE CAKE STIR-FRY
FOR THE RICE CAKE LOVER
WITH JYP'S SIGNATURE PINKISH PLASTIC PANTS
It's as if
someone took them off and ran away.
Now that I look at the pants again,
they now seem quite shabby.
-It looked good when it was just finished.
-Yes.
-They look like plastic pants.
-It's almost like sausage.
-Or maybe cuttlefish.
-Cuttlefish?
It feels like this.
Someone I love
spent days
making a cute little ring.
But just before I got that,
-I got a few-carat diamond ring.
-From someone else.
-He's unsure if it'll be intriguing.
-You can't beat a diamond.
I'm so moved by the effort, but what now?
The rich guy came by.
"The rich guy"?
DID YOU LOVE
YONG-WOOK'S MEAT DIAMOND THAT MUCH?
-What should I eat first?
-Actually,
the food surrounding the pants
symbolizes your fans.
SO MOVED
-He's starting to make a story.
-I get it.
Did you come up with it now?
-That was what I intended.
-It was?
His favorite food is rice cake,
and he must love his fans just as much.
-I'm now on the stage in plastic pants.
-You're there.
And my fans are screaming my name.
They're standing there to watch the show.
You're right.
TRYING THE LEFT LEG FIRST
-The plastic pants may be…
-The leg first.
-The left leg.
-He tries the left leg first.
He's cutting the edge off.
You can eat that too.
-They're too long.
-You might have to use your teeth.
-That's a nice cut.
-The plastic and the meatball?
You have to eat them together.
-The pants.
-What now?
-I'm nervous.
-"What now?"
-I'm sure he's curious.
-He must be half excited, half worried.
Dip it slightly in the sauce.
He's someone
who can't hide the look on his face.
With the love of his fans.
This is after he saw the diamond.
WHAT'S THE LEFT LEG LIKE?
He used ramyeon soup base for the sauce.
-He poured it in.
-It looks good.
Now, that's a dish
with a very intense flavor.
He's so serious.
…CHUCKLE
SMILES AUTOMATICALLY
-That's it. He makes you smile.
-"What is this?"
Why does everyone smile
after eating Poong's dish?
He just had the plastic pants.
It's either really delicious
or he's in plain disbelief.
WHAT DOES HIS SMILE MEAN?
-What now?
-"What now?"
-What is it?
-If it's not good, that's too bad.
Just consider his effort.
-Is it too salty?
-The idea deserves a full mark.
-He tried hard.
It's a shame that these are burnt.
-The burn.
-The burnt flavor must hit you hard.
If only it weren't burnt…
But it delivers accurately.
The message?
Let me try it once more.
-Try the right side.
-The intention is clear to him.
It feels like
your fans especially loved
the lower half of your body.
IT LOOKS LIKE
THEY'RE CHEERING FOR HIS LOWER HALF
He tries it one more time.
FOCUSED WITH CHOPSTICKS IN HIS HAND
-The message is clear.
-He gets the intention.
It doesn't beat around the bush.
That's it.
Poong doesn't do anything unnecessary.
I'm kind of curious.
Can you try just the pants?
-Just the pants?
-The plastic?
That's just starch.
No, he added kimchi too.
It might taste like kimchi jeon.
That might be surprisingly delicious.
-It's probably chewy.
-The legs were burnt, so…
WHAT ARE THE PLASTIC PANTS LIKE?
Just the plastic pants.
CHEWING
He likes rice cake,
so he might be okay with that.
Does it taste like anything?
It's really well-made.
THE PLASTIC PANTS WERE PERFECT
It wasn't made just for display.
It's made so well.
-This plastic.
-It must be chewy.
In comparison,
the filling could've been better.
What a shame.
-Next, he tries his fans' love.
-The love.
J. Y. Park the Rice Cake Gorilla.
So? Your fans' love.
ALSO PLEASED
Gosh.
It's so good.
The pork and rice cake
go really well together.
It tastes simple,
but it isn't juvenile.
Both dishes must've been
therapeutic for you.
Why don't we try some pants too?
Let us evaluate it as well.
First, the pork neck,
Director Yong-wook's dish, SeYP.
SeYP.
HEAVILY TOPPED WITH SAUCE
MMM
WAKING UP
I see what it's like.
AUTOMATICALLY AMAZED
The Kimchi is different.
-Yes, it is.
-It's especially crunchy.
I love the sauce so much.
-The sauce.
-I want to take it home.
I think it'll go well
with both Western and Korean cuisine.
Why am I extra hungry today?
I want more.
I could smell the smoky aroma
until the moment I swallowed the food.
I smelled it the whole time
while I was chewing it.
This with a glass of makgeolli…
REMINDED OF MAKGEOLLI
-Makgeolli.
-That's it.
Actually, a truly good story
is a story that you thought you knew
but isn't the same as you thought it was.
It was the same with this dish.
We thought we knew this well,
but we didn't know it could go this far.
He's receiving a lot of great compliments.
Next, please try the plastic pants.
…CHUCKLE
ONE BITE
The leg and the pants.
ANOTHER BITE
He made the legs
with kimchi and pork belly.
GATHERING EVERYTHING
AND EATS IT IN A BITE
The pants have a crazy texture.
-It's good.
-It's really chewy.
It's like dak-galbi.
Or tteok-kkochi.
Kimchi jeon.
Kimchi fried rice on a steel plate.
ALL KINDS OF DELICIOUS DISHES
It looks crudely made,
but the balance is quite nice.
It has saltiness,
-sweetness, and sourness. It was good.
-And spiciness.
The way he made the plastic pants
-is exactly how you make starch sheets.
-Yes, it's the starch sheets.
-This wasn't groundless.
-It's that texture.
He has learned stuff
over people's shoulders.
It tasted quite hot,
just like the WATERBOMB Festival.
So he's performing at the festival,
but it's actually held in Tongin Market.
WATER BOMB FESTIVAL AT TONGIN MARKET
DOING WAVES
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE MARKETPLACE
-That market is famous for oil tteokbokki.
-Oil tteokbokki.
I just tried
the crotch of the pants,
and it felt like a fan
trying to hold on to his pants.
That picture came to my mind.
He's dying to be funny.
Everyone felt something different.
You're a good talker.
-All right.
-He's good.
Now, it's time to vote.
Press one for Director Yoo Yong-wook
and two for Kim Poong.
Make your decision and press the button!
Before I do that,
I want to leave you with this.
I also didn't get formal musical training.
Of course, I learned from Kim Hyung-suk,
but no formal education.
So I believe in the unorthodox.
-He has respect for the unorthodox.
-That's awesome.
-That was so cool.
-All right, then.
Press one for Yong-wook and two for Poong.
Press one!
-He pressed one.
-He decides quickly.
And now, let's find out
who J. Y. Park chose!
Show us!
Not half air, half sound,
but Half Pork, Half Kimchi!
A dish that comforted his heart.
Was it Poong's plastic pants?
Or was it Yong-wook's smoked dishes?
I can't tell.
Who did J. Y. Park choose?
-Who won?
-Who did he choose?
YOO YONG-WOOK WINS
DIRECTOR YOO YONG-WOOK'S SEYP WINS
Director Yong-wook wins.
-Great job.
-Thank you.
Thank you.
BEATS THE GATEKEEPER
AND CLAIMS HIS FIRST WIN
No matter how delicious his dish is,
I thought the act of smoking the food
was a bit unrelated to Korean cuisine
and wouldn't go well with the food.
But it had a surprising effect
of bringing out more Korean flavors
from the ingredients.
That was shocking.
I'm a bit dazed right now.
I have done everything
I possibly could today,
so it's just a wonder
how you come up with new ideas every week.
I have so much respect for everyone.
I see.
May I leave a word for Poong?
This idea itself was impossible.
As I mentioned before,
the plastic pants proved
that his cooking skills
should not be taken too lightly.
She said that's how you make
Chinese starch sheets.
Thank you very much.
You must be quite disappointed.
The plastic pants turned out so well.
I'm fine.
I had tons of fun today.
So yes, it was fun.
THE PLASTIC PANTS WILL GO DOWN IN HISTORY
They were both cool.
YOO YONG-WOOK TAKES HIS FIRST STAR
-He wins his debut match! Congrats!
-Congratulations.
COMING UP: PREVIEW FOR
UHM JUNG-HWA & SOOYOUNG'S EPISODE
TODAY'S FRIDGE OWNERS
CHOI SOOYOUNG & UHM JUNG-HWA
That's what I'm talking about.
I can't look at her.
What are you doing?
Everything he says sounds like a lie.
ON TOP OF THAT
-You probably weren't a huge fan.
-Me?
What's my debut project?
I forgot the title.
HIS TRUE COLORS FINALLY SHOW
His credibility just dropped.
She's now suspicious of Sung-jun.
TO CAPTURE SOOYOUNG'S HEART,
THE CHEFS DEPLOY DIFFERENT STRATEGIES
SHAKING HIS HEAD VIOLENTLY
TASTE OF HER OWN MEDICINE
ENERGY!
MAKING AN IMPRESSION
She's addicted to dancing.
-What are you up to?
-Go away!
I'LL SHOW YOU WHAT I CAN REALLY DO!
RISKING EVERYTHING TO LOOK COOL
OH, MY GOSH
DID IT WORK?
IS THERE A PROBLEM?
WHICH CHEF WILL SHE CHOOSE?
You had us scared there.
I've always dreamed
of this moment since childhood.
"Into the New World" with her.
I decline.
We also don't want to see it.
Subtitle translation by: Eunsook Youn